[{"answer": "You do of course try on, when you buy", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh, you don't recall", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, she's really great. I mean, she's got like a real warmth about her and she's really bright and really pretty and uh...the conversation though, I mean, it was...talking with her is like talking with you, but, ya know, obviously much better", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh, nothing happened, ya know, but it was great", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " So, ya know, what, what happened", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh, nothing happened, but it was..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " What, are you serious...why, why did she call", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "To be polite? You are insane", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " So why did she call", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "To be polite, I rest my case", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm not gonna watch you do laundry", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Come on, I'm tired", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What is that? It's ridiculous!  You don't even know, what hotel she's staying at, you can't call her. That's a signal, my friend, that's a signal!  Signal", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Maybe I'm right? Of course I'm right", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "This is insane. You know, I don't even know where she's staying! She, she's not gonna call me, this is unbelievable", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No no no, don't interrupt the cycle. The machine is working, it, it knows what it's doing, just let it finish", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Hey, I'm sorry, I...ya know, I, I thought you knew... You got any meat", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " What happened? Well, they STUNK, that's what happened!  Ya know, I almost wound up going to that game", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Look, it's a very awkward situation, I, I don't wanna be presumptuous", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "All right, she said she couldn't find a decent hote", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "A decent hote", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You can't be serious. This is that place cit", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, OK. Oh, wait a second. Oh, I, I forgot to clean the bathroom", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Now, how could that be good", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What a world that would be, if you just could ask a woman what she's thinkin'", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Listen, listen, don't get worked up, 'cause you're gonna know the whole story the minute she steps off the plane", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "\"Li", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Hug is definitely good", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Ya know how they do that", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Shake is bad, but what if it's the", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Uh, no, yeah, go right ahead.", "docId": "Seinfeld-Good-News_-Bad-News.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Uh, yeah, yeah, sure, why don't you stay? Yeah, uhm...What is your, what is your schedule for tomorrow? Are you, are you doin' anything", "qsentId": 32}]